I can be an engine buzzing like a bee, I'm a real independent
Doing the laundry and planning for the future
It's the nature of a renaissance girl
I can be your darling cooking you dinner and soothing your heartache
Having three kinds and still remain a virgin
It's my version of a renaissance girl

Lift me lift me up when the air is thin and my mind will take off
Pull me pull me down when my love is pure and I feel alright now

Come along, come, come along, we can be your renaissance girls
Come along, come, come along, move forward, move forward
Come along, come, come along, tough like rocks and sweet like pearls
Come along, come, come along, we can be your renaissance girls

I can be an artist sculpting your face like you always wanted
Making you believe it's just how I saw it
It's logic for a renaissance girl
I can be impressed by all the things you know'
I'm fan I'm obsessed now
I'm in your I drive in your fast car
It's mastered by a renaissance girl

I'll release my mind you can be my back bone
I call you honey you can cry on my shoulder
Let it all breath, I got a degree in psychology

Lift me lift me up when the air is thin and my mind will take off
Pull me pull me down when my love is gone and I feel alright now

Come along, come, come along, we can be your renaissance girls
Come along, come, come along, move on, move on
Come along, come, come along, take the drugs
Come along, come, come along we can be your renaissance girls

Sangskrivere: Nanna Fabricius
Renaissance Girls sangtekster � Sony/ATV Music Publishing LLC
